we have to be some of the most resilient people
because there's so many ups and downs in gardening
you know
change of climate change of temperature
changing in the seasons
you know it's in a very hot summer that
that really test your skill
as a gardener or as a farmer
you know
and really test your love for this thing
and sometimes we have to relocate
and our new location don't
don't do well for our plants
there's so many obstacles
yeah I remember even one time
I got like 24 strawberry plants
and I'm saying you know what
at least five of these must survive
and one by one they just die
they just die off slowly and I tried everything
I try changing the soil
I try changing location you know
I try watering some more I try watering some less
I try different methods man
and they just die off one by one every day
breaks your heart a little bit each time until
you know and crush that vision I'm like oh yeah
one day I'm gonna have all these strawberries
and it's gonna be delicious
and all the things you can make strawberry jam...
all of that just get crushed bit by bit
the same thing happen with a sage plant
a few sage plants that I got the seed and sowed them
and they all popped up
and they just die off one by one
it don't no matter what I did
it's very very heartbreaking
a lot of things I go through
with with with um gardening
and with farming and with working in the greenhouse
a lot of things
let me understand why some people just...